Yen Ting Wu

Software Engineer

a9600125a@gmail.com







My name is YenTing Wu, a self-taught software engineer and a creator. My passion for being a software engineer lies in coming up with brilliant ideas with my colleges and enabling them. I take good care about experience, design and communication.

I am also an open-source collaborator, mainly contribute to React community. I currently work with Chakra UI team to build the doc site and maintain DevRel. I love to collaborate with people coming from different backgrounds but having the same goal - Building a better community.

Outside of programming, I love river trekking, biking in summer and exploring wild hot spring in winter. Nature always inspires me.

Projects

FoF

A brand new dating app.

Expo React Native Zustand React Query



420

A gallery for me to play with design skills and libraries. Mainly built with THREE.JS and p5.

NextJS Chakra UI THREE

Procrastination archive

A productivity app to help me understand how FE, BE and DevOps work together.





NextJS Chakra UI Zustand React Query Node Docker



Work Experience

StarkTech UI Engineer

Aug 2020 - Jan 2021

Designed and developed a food delivery platform with Expo and GatsbyJS

- Developed a web-based client-side food order system with GatsbyJS
- Developed mobile-based apps with Expo and React Native

Open Source Experience

Chakra UI Collaborator

Sep 2021 - Present

In Docs & DevRel team

- Developed the site's with new features and maintain the performance
 - Recent PR Create Showcase Page
- Improve docs to make use cases more clearly

Stacks

Front End React, Svelte

Back End Node, Gin, PostgresQL, Serverless, Docker

Mobile Expo, React Native

DevOps Firebase, Droplets, Heroku Language Typescript, Javascript, Go

Education

Soochow University

Business Administration (B.A.)

Sep 2015 - Jun 2019